[Music]
[音乐]
okay so this is the non washed page so
好吧，这是未洗的页面，所以
this talk if you're in the right place
如果你来对地方了
is about distributed tracing and
关于分布式跟踪和
different than some of the talks I've
与我的一些演讲不同
done before this one is less code and
在此代码较少之前完成
more about what people are doing like
关于人们的行为的更多信息
how they're how they roll out things and
他们是如何推出事物的，以及
where to find information about that
在哪里可以找到有关的信息
it's a goal is to kind of connect to to
它的目标是要连接到
real life because you know we live in
现实生活，因为你知道我们生活在
this worlds with natives and clouds and
这个世界有本地人和云
things and it's good to find some
东西，找到一些东西很好
concrete information sometimes hopefully
有时希望获得具体信息
yo tell me if I've achieved this goal or
告诉我我是否达到了这个目标，或者
not I'm Adrian I work on the sprink law
不，我是Adrian，我从事洒水法工作
team at pivotal with some colleagues
与一些同事一起工作的团队
you've probably seen sessions from today
您可能看过今天的会议
and tomorrow I'm focused on distributed
明天我会专注于分布式
tracing since at pivotal maybe almost
追踪，因为在关键时刻
three and a half years now but before
三年半现在但以前
that also when I was at Twitter we were
当我在Twitter上时
the last project I worked on was
我从事的最后一个项目是
something called Zipkin and Zipkin is a
叫做Zipkin和Zipkin的东西是
turkish word for harpoon-like that you
像鱼叉一样的土耳其语单词
throw at a whale and they made this
扔鲸鱼，他们做到了
tracing system to find out why the fail
跟踪系统以找出失败的原因
whale would show up in the in the apps
鲸鱼会显示在应用程序中
back then and that was a project I
那时那是我的一个项目
didn't start but I helped move it into
没有开始，但我帮助将其移入
more open source so firstly how many
更多的开源，首先是多少
people here have worked with distributed
这里的人已经与分布式
tracing before okay a lot of you and how
跟踪很多人之前，以及如何
many does that mean sleuth okay yeah
难道这意味着侦探好吗
some people so I will try not to belabor
有些人，所以我会尽量不要lab惜
too much but I think there probably some
太多了，但我认为可能有些
people who you might need a very quick
您可能需要非常快的人
primer
底漆
also I'll try to leave some time at the
我也会尝试在
end I know there will be pressure
最后我知道会有压力
between me and the beer but if you want
在我和啤酒之间，但如果你想
to run into beers you can you can take
碰上啤酒就可以
me with you well so but firstly you know
我和你在一起很好，但是首先你知道
for I think four years which is not a
因为我认为四年不是
long time in in application performance
长时间的应用程序性能
stuff many people have been doing this
很多人一直在做的事情
for like 20 years but for me it's been
大约20年了，但对我来说
four or something like that each year I
我每年四岁左右
find it easier to say what tracing is
发现它更容易说出什么是追踪
but it's always difficult here's the
但是这总是很困难
current best slide I can come up with
我能拿出的当前最佳幻灯片
with what are the most important things
最重要的是什么
to think about this versus something
考虑这个与某事
else and you can read it for yourself
否则，您可以自己阅读
but the idea is firstly the tracking
但首先是追踪
nature and it's going across hosts and
自然，它跨越了主机和
like like correlation you have a tracing
就像相关性一样，您可以进行跟踪
ID but the most important thing is that
ID，但最重要的是
you can achieve causal relationships
你可以建立因果关系
meaning that you can tell specifically
意思是您可以明确地说出
what requests resulted in another one
什么要求导致了另一个
independent of time so it's not it's not
与时间无关，所以不是
dependent on clocks being synchronized
取决于时钟是否同步
or anything and so you can draw pretty
或任何东西，所以你可以画漂亮
diagrams and look at them too to help
并查看它们也有帮助
you blame other people for what your
你责怪别人
problems have and maybe there will be
有问题，也许会有
some things that are easier to see in a
一些比较容易看清的东西
way displayed as images as opposed to
显示为图像的方式与
like log lines and the why do I care
像日志行，为什么我在乎
slide is another one that's subject to
幻灯片是另一个
thrash over the years because people
多年来because动，因为人们
care about different things and this
关心不同的事情，这
will follow up with some examples from
将跟进一些例子
from actual quotes from people but most
根据人们的实际报价，但大多数
of the time I think people are most
当时我认为人们是最
interested in a triage meaning I want to
对分流感兴趣，我想
know what's most important about this
知道什么是最重要的
problem so I can focus my time on that
问题，所以我可以把时间集中在
and it had achieves this by
它已经通过实现
contextualizing errors within the
范围内的上下文错误
context of what call came in first does
先来电话的上下文
it matter
没关系
and other things like time like how long
时间等多久
did it take people also care because it
它是否也需要人们的照顾，因为
can help you visualize time in service
可以帮助您可视化服务时间
because maybe we have SLA concerns and
因为也许我们有SLA问题，
we want to make sure that our service is
我们想确保我们的服务是
performing but we also want to know if
表演，但我们也想知道是否
if others are being impacted by us or we
如果其他人受到我们的影响
are impacting others so the idea of
正在影响他人，所以
visualizing the relationships between
可视化之间的关系
you and and your services that you may
您以及您可能提供的服务
be blocking or blocking on and
被阻止或阻止
increasingly this this fourth bullet is
这第四颗子弹越来越多
probably going to promote to the top
可能会晋升到顶部
because applications are getting more
因为应用越来越多
complex you know they're breaking into
复杂，你知道他们正在闯入
smaller pieces on ephemeral you know as
短暂的小块，你知道
ephemeral as a function call now and not
暂时作为函数调用，现在不
just the architecture things like lambda
只是像lambda这样的架构
or whatnot but also just the nature of
还是什么，但仅仅是
how we're coding we're doing reactive
我们如何编码，我们正在做反应式
and that's also cool but it's quite hard
这也很酷，但是很难
to track where where things are
追踪事物在哪里
happening if things occur during
如果事情发生在
assembly time of your functional
功能的组装时间
compositions or a runtime and tracing
合成或运行时和跟踪
can help you understand what actually
可以帮助您了解实际情况
happened at least and so besides the
至少发生了，所以除了
individual requests another common
个人要求另一个共同点
reason people care is that they can see
人们关心的原因是他们可以看到
their architecture I wouldn't say that
他们的建筑，我不会说
someone looks at a image of their
有人看着他们的图像
architecture and has like this brilliant
建筑，并拥有这样的辉煌
insight by looking at five thousand
五千眼见识
things connected to each other but there
东西互相连接，但在那里
are some values in here mainly if you
这里的一些值主要是如果你
think about what are the sources of
考虑一下哪些来源
traffic in coming to your service and
交通来为您服务和
what are you calling out to even if it's
你在呼唤什么
on one only one level deep this is
在一个只有一个层次的深度上，这是
important there's more details about
重要的是有更多的细节
this I'll get to but I think this is
我会去的，但我认为这是
sort of like the intro of why a lot of
有点像为什么很多的介绍
people care
人们关心
I mean besides you know you can probably
我的意思是，除了你知道你可能
get stickers with distributed tracing I
获得带有分布式跟踪的标签I
think I have one yeah oh sorry there is
以为我有一个，对不起，有
important I did that so distributed
重要的是我做到了这么分散
tracing like many things is full of
像许多事物一样追踪
jargon the the worst one is spam
术语最糟糕的是垃圾邮件
and so if you see this word it is not
所以如果你看到这个词，那不是
like spam but it is basically describing
就像垃圾邮件，但它基本上是在描述
one operation within the set of others
其他操作集中的一个操作
and and you know it's most important
而且你知道这是最重要的
fact it's time
事实到了
but it's contextualized like metrics
但它像指标一样在上下文中
with with tags like can tell you about
与之类的标签可以告诉您有关
the HTTP call or what whatever it is
HTTP调用或它是什么
actually representing and the trace is
实际代表的轨迹是
these things connected together and
这些东西连接在一起，
they're usually showing you latency
他们通常向您显示延迟
relationships but definitely calls or
关系，但肯定是电话或
relationships another jargon is that the
关系另一个行话是
word tracer you may see that coming up
文字追踪器，您可能会看到
and it's not like that when you've done
完成后就不是那样了
all these drugs and your can no longer
所有这些药物，您将不再能
see straight it's the the library that
看得直是图书馆
actually is doing the work like a
实际上是像
logging library and its job is to record
日志记录库，其工作是记录
this and pass context around so that
并传递上下文，以便
you're if you think that the call goes
如果您认为电话接通了
from here to there that it actually did
从这里到那里，实际上
an instrumentation is actually a shared
仪器实际上是共享的
term between tracing and metrics really
跟踪和指标之间的术语
they have exactly the same focus which
他们有完全相同的重点
is to bind the insight about how a
是要结合关于如何
library operates into things that it's
图书馆运作成它的东西
reporting in the case of tracing it's
在跟踪情况下进行报告
it's spans but in case of like
这是跨度，但在像
micrometer or something it will be you
千分尺或它会是你
know gauges or or counters or whatnot
知道量规或计数器或其他
but instrumentation is the thing that
但是仪器是
hooks into your library is to record
钩入您的图书馆是为了记录
things
东西
so span like we know we've got the if
所以跨度就像我们知道我们有如果
it's a HTTP call it's like post and then
这是一个HTTP调用，就像发布，然后
the end point information some cluster
终点信息集群
maybe some IP addresses and tags you
也许一些IP地址和标签
might look up with tracing is capturing
可能会查找正在捕获的跟踪
those things and you know it's in the
这些东西，你知道它在
tracers are going to be recording this
示踪剂将记录下来
and I'm showing color here you know
我在这里显示颜色
highlighting that I'm not very sensitive
强调我不是很敏感
to people with colorblindness but the
对于有色盲的人
the gray one is one host and then the
灰色的是一台主机，然后
more gray one is a different host so the
灰色的主机是另一台主机，因此
idea is that a tracer actually lives on
想法是示踪剂实际上存在于
one host like so if you're in spring
一位主人喜欢，如果你在春天
world your spring boot app will have a
世界您的春季启动应用程序将有一个
tracer inside that sleuth is controlling
侦探内部正在控制的示踪剂
and that's going to be sending data that
这将发送数据
that it can see which is only the data
它可以看到仅是数据
from that process and then there would
从那个过程中，然后
be another process you know that you're
是另一个过程，你知道你是
calling maybe and then that will have
打电话也许然后
its own tracer they're independent so
它自己的示踪剂是独立的，因此
they're not sharing like a cluster
他们没有像集群一样共享
between them or anything what happens is
他们之间或发生的任何事情是
that they when you make a call from one
当您打来电话时，他们
host to another
主持另一个
it adds things like if it's HTTP will
它会添加一些类似HTTP的内容
add headers saying what trace ID I'm in
添加标头，说明我所在的跟踪ID
and those will be passed to your
这些将传递给您
downstream so if you see here for
下游，所以如果你在这里看到
example the routes that no parent makes
示例没有父母的路线
a call in the same process using maybe
在同一过程中使用
thread locals or something but if it
线程本地人或其他东西，但如果有的话
goes across it's gonna pass exact same
穿过它会完全一样
IDs but it might be over headers the IDs
ID，但可能在ID的标头上方
are the important things these are the
这些是重要的事情
things that allow you to link the calls
可以链接电话的东西
relationship just in case you may have a
关系，以防万一您可能有一个
thousand things happening at the same
千件事同时发生
time and and the timestamps won't help
时间和时间戳将无济于事
you they're the actual of data the
你是数据的实际
important parts like the things that
重要的部分，例如那些
tell you what HTTP request it was that
告诉你那是什么HTTP请求
sent out event a synchronously
同步发出事件
so this manages you overhead in the
因此，这可以管理您在
critical path carried
关键路径
the actual big JSON stuff they're sent
他们发送的实际大JSON内容
asynchronously that's how it works
异步就是这样
and so if you turning it on you're
所以如果你打开它
turning on a utility library the tracer
打开实用程序库的跟踪器
if you're using spring boot you're
如果您使用的是弹簧靴，
usually having spring cloud sleuth do
平时有春云探秘
this for you you may not even know
这对你来说你甚至可能都不知道
what's happening and that
发生了什么事
instrumentation the framework specific
特定于框架的检测
code you either configuring it or
编码您配置它或
something like sue is configuring it for
像sue这样的配置
you and and then that at the end of the
你，然后在最后
day is pointed somewhere to throw this
指着某天扔这个
stuff and some people will just throw it
东西，有些人会把它扔掉
in their logs but most of the time you
在他们的日志中，但是大多数时候
would send it to a tracing system as it
会将其发送到跟踪系统
begin being one of those this is a
开始成为其中之一，这是一个
screenshot of our lovely evolving new UI
我们可爱的不断发展的新用户界面的屏幕截图
called lens and this is a real trace how
叫做镜头，这是真实的痕迹
many here have ever used a sass called
这里很多人曾经用过一个叫做
type form to complete forms well you
输入表格以完成表格
should support your local businesses
应该支持您的本地业务
this is a Barcelona company so anyway
这是一家巴塞罗那公司，所以
this is our this is actually a live
这是我们这实际上是一个现场
trace I got from someone today in
我今天从某人那里得到的踪迹
Barcelona and this is explaining a
巴塞罗那，这说明了
request into their service platform they
要求他们进入他们的服务平台
have API proxy and you can see the whole
有API代理，您可以看到整个
request took 50 and 1/2 milliseconds
请求花费了50毫秒和1/2毫秒
hitting 3 services with a width called
击中3个服务的宽度称为
depth max of 6 with 10 operations
最多10个操作的最大深度为6
happening and you can see this is a mini
发生了，你可以看到这是一个迷你
map actually maybe not needed and a
地图实际上可能不需要，并且
trace this small but if you have
追踪这个小但是如果你有
something that's hitting like 70
就像70
services you might need a mini map to
您可能需要一张小地图的服务
like get to the right spot in this case
喜欢在这种情况下到达正确的位置
I asked him like can you show me like a
我问他像你能给我看一个像
trace that has an error in it that it
跟踪其中有一个错误
would be easier to explain so in this
这样会更容易解释
case the red means error at the bottom
如果红色表示底部错误
so somehow they call to get teams of
所以他们以某种方式打电话来让
mine erred but if you know how to read
我犯了错，但是如果你知道怎么读
this and you know red means error I know
这个，你知道红色意味着错误，我知道
that I can't blame the queries because
我不能怪查询，因为
they all succeeded so something else
他们都成功了，还有别的
calls the failure maybe some code maybe
调用失败也许是一些代码
no pointer exception after the database
数据库后无指针异常
queries return if you know how to read a
如果您知道如何读取查询，则返回查询
trace you can easily contextualize
跟踪您可以轻松地将其上下文化
things and I'm not this is not like a
事情，我不是，这不像一个
class on how to to use tracing I'm just
关于如何使用跟踪的课程，我只是
trying to look at one real-life thing to
试图看一眼现实生活
show Zipkin is is a you know kit can be
显示Zipkin是一个您知道的工具包
deployed as easily as a single file even
甚至可以像单个文件一样轻松部署
though we don't recommend people just
尽管我们不建议人们
using our in memory option we often have
使用我们的内存选项，我们经常
people do things that we explicitly say
人们做我们明确说过的事情
don't as if can it happens to be a
不要好像碰巧是一个
spring buta plication and so you can
春天的butaplication，所以你可以
start it quite quite simply but the
非常简单地启动它，但是
focus of this talk wasn't really like
这次演讲的重点不是很像
that I did need to do some introductions
我确实需要做一些介绍
here and spend 15 minutes doing that but
在这里花15分钟来做，但是
here's the the meat of it was a typical
这是典型的肉
site look like ok so it's nice to see
该网站看起来还可以，所以很高兴看到
images and things but what does it mean
图片和事物，但这意味着什么
to people and when I talk about a site
给人们，当我谈论一个网站时
what I mean is like a production
我的意思是像生产
deployment and you know specifically why
部署，您知道为什么
what would make it a zip you know site
是什么让它成为您知道的zip网站
it means that there's some part of this
这意味着其中有一部分
ecosystem that they rely on you know as
他们所依赖的生态系统
some parts that that we as a community
我们作为社区的某些部分
produce life is dirty it's not like you
产生生活是肮脏的，这不像你
use only one thing like I have this with
只用一件事
one date library and I need nothing else
一个日期库，我什么也不需要
because obviously you need to put it
因为显然你需要把它放
inside of a server you need to deploy
在您需要部署的服务器内部
the server there's many things that we
服务器上有很多东西
use to make our things work so Zipkin is
用来使我们的东西起作用，所以Zipkin是
it lives among these things and by site
它生活在这些事物之中，并依地点而定
owner what I mean is that even though
老板我的意思是尽管
people have many jobs there's usually
人们有很多工作，通常
someone who is actually more interested
实际上更感兴趣的人
in something like tracing or maybe their
在诸如追踪或他们的
tasks to do it so by site owner I mean
网站所有者要做的任务，我的意思是
like this that person who's responsible
像这样负责的人
and specifically the ones who tend to
特别是那些倾向于
publish information back to the
将信息发布回
community or are pretty involved in the
社区或相当参与
community so that means that they're
社区，这意味着他们
they're actually contributing back and
他们实际上在回馈
in some way even if it's just knowledge
以某种方式，即使只是知识
about what's going on so if we think
关于发生了什么，所以如果我们想
about this when you know one of the
当你知道其中一个
things about this presentation I was
关于这次演讲的一些事情
taking information from our wiki so we
从我们的Wiki获取信息，因此我们
have a wiki about called
有一个关于的维基
called sites and I can give you the link
叫网站，我可以给你链接
I think it's in the slide deck but we
我认为它在滑盖中，但是我们
just rolled the dice and said okay what
刚刚掷骰子说好吧
if we ask people to give us information
如果我们要求人们给我们信息
would they actually do it and so here's
他们会实际这样做吗，所以这里是
some questions that people who did
那些做过的人的一些问题
answer about like what is their company
像他们的公司一样回答
doing and like how do they set up their
做，喜欢他们如何建立自己的
kit like what what type of things are
工具包是什么类型的东西
important to them like what type of data
对他们来说很重要，例如什么类型的数据
are they actually using like because
他们真的在用吗，因为
sometimes you you capture a lot of
有时候你会捕获很多
information but you don't read any of it
信息，但您没有阅读任何信息
so what is the actual important stuff
那么真正重要的东西是什么
from from what's just being collected
从刚刚收集的东西中
and some statistics about like you know
和一些统计数据，如你所知
what what does it cost them so let's
他们花了多少钱，所以让我们
think about some things that happen with
想想发生的一些事情
within systems like if you're collecting
在系统中，例如您正在收集
if you're like running a logging system
如果您想运行日志系统
you'll need to know how much data you're
您需要知道多少数据
gonna be able to afford to keep and for
能够负担得起并保持
how long and what are your rules around
你要遵守多长时间？
that similar things happen and tracing
类似的事情发生并追踪
although usually the data retention is
尽管通常数据保留是
quite short maybe seven days the things
很短的也许七天的事情
that are very very different from site
与网站有很大不同
to site or like how people name their
定位或喜欢人们如何命名他们的
services if we go back to like a thing
服务，如果我们回到喜欢的东西
like this like these names right
像这些名字一样
they you can name things anything like
他们你可以给任何东西起名字
when I worked at Twitter there were
当我在Twitter工作时
birds and like you know obviously what
鸟类，就像你一样，很清楚
happens in companies is like they get
公司发生的事情就像他们得到
big and then eventually some SVP says
大，然后最终一些高级副总裁说
okay no more silly names you must name
好的，不再需要愚蠢的名字了
the thing and now you have to rename the
东西，现在您必须重命名
things and and so like service naming is
诸如此类，例如服务命名
not like a problem in tracing but it
不像追踪中的问题，但它
becomes more of a problem if you don't
如果您不这样做，将成为更大的问题
have a good service name so like one
有一个很好的服务名称，就像一个
thing that's very funny is that you kind
有趣的是你善良
of inherit the problems of your normal
继承你正常的问题
architecture when you start plotting
开始绘图时的体系结构
them on graphs and such what type of
他们在图上，这样的类型
site specific tags so like if I'm
网站专用标签，例如
running McDonald's maybe like Big Macs
像麦当劳一样经营麦当劳
per second is actually pretty important
每秒实际上很重要
fact for me but like maybe it's also
对我来说是事实，但也许也是
important if I'm now working at
如果我现在在工作很重要
McDonald's you know actually there's
麦当劳，你知道实际上有
really contextual right so actually is
实际上是上下文相关的权利，实际上是
it can allow you to to make sure that
它可以让您确保
index is we have a function called
索引是我们有一个叫做
autocomplete tags so you can train it to
自动完成标记，因此您可以将其训练为
to capture Big Macs if you want but at
捕捉巨无霸，如果你想要的话
any rate like there's there's
像那里那样的任何比率
another thing is very interesting about
另一件事很有趣
sites is that everybody's in a different
网站是每个人都在不同的地方
place like you're just getting started
像刚开始一样的地方
are you in like maintenance mode and in
您是否处于维护模式并处于
our whole point about capturing site
关于捕获网站的整个观点
information is to allow people like
信息是为了让人们喜欢
yourselves if someone is is not it
自己是不是有人
sounds like actually a lot of people are
听起来实际上很多人
using tracing already but anyway
已经使用跟踪但仍然使用
wherever you are in the path there's
无论您在哪里，都有
probably someone who's not where you're
可能不在你身旁的人
at yet or who's a bit farther and
现在还是谁更远
sharing knowledge is really helpful
分享知识真的很有帮助
anyway why bother
无论如何为什么要打扰
so ascend is like financial services
所以上升就像金融服务
company they you know they said like
他们知道的公司他们说
what was their use like what is their
他们的用途是什么
story that they say about why they're
他们说出自己为什么的故事
doing what they're doing and you know
做他们在做什么，你知道
it's interesting what words people
人们说什么很有趣
choose so in their case they're in one
选择，在他们的情况下，他们合二为一
of these like digital transformation
其中包括数字化转型
things like do people say digital
人们说数字化之类的事情
transformation here in Spain also I
在西班牙的改造我
think I hear it everywhere but like yeah
认为我到处都能听到，但是像是的
refactoring everything and so can you
重构一切，你也可以
find out whether your service is
找出您的服务是否
performing worse now because it doesn't
现在表现不佳，因为它不会
always perform better does it so you can
总是表现更好，所以你可以
look at an individual service calls just
看一个单独的服务电话
to see whether it's actually impact
看看是否真的有影响
impacting in the right direction or not
是否朝正确的方向冲击
and also this idea of like
还有这个想法
non-conformance service communications
不合格服务通信
that's a very like financial service
这非常像金融服务
etype of word right but what that means
正确的单词类型，但这意味着什么
is that is your application actually
那是你的应用程序吗
making connections that shouldn't be
建立不应该的连接
making so if for example Europe you you
因此，例如欧洲
have someone walking around and with
有人走来走去
with a mesh shaped hammer and like
用网状锤子之类的
smacking mesh on things and saying like
在物体上打孔并说
the mesh is doing everything and then
网格正在做所有事情，然后
you actually look at your traffic and
你实际上看你的流量
it's not using the mesh it's just going
它不使用网格而只是去
wherever it feels like this tracing can
无论在哪里进行跟踪
help you find that right because you can
帮助您找到正确的方法，因为您可以
actually see the network connections of
实际看到的网络连接
those making and you would be able to
那些使您能够
tell whether or not your application is
告诉您的应用程序是否
in fact using the mesh at all and so so
实际上完全使用了网格等等
there's there's a basically deviation
基本上有偏差
from the design was one of the important
从设计是重要的之一
things because they're going through to
事情，因为他们正在经历
that hotels.com was like you know
hotels.com就像你知道的
they're looking for you know the the
他们正在寻找你知道的
low-hanging fruit
低垂的果实
looking at that's more like a service
看起来更像是一项服务
level triage like so if you're looking
水平分类，如果您正在寻找
to find out who you know where your
找出你知道谁的人
low-hanging fruit are so if you're
低挂的水果是这样，如果你是
running anything as booking related and
运行与预订相关的任何内容，以及
you're making a customer wait for all of
您正在让客户等待所有
the things to happen tracing is awesome
跟踪发生的事情很棒
for this because a lot of your
为此，因为你很多
downstreams can be quite slow and so
下游可能很慢，所以
pipelining those can be very easy it's
流水线操作可能非常容易
sometimes extremely difficult with
有时很难
especially with async libraries that
特别是与异步库
we're using we may not know if it may
我们正在使用我们可能不知道是否可能
look really reactive and everything but
看起来真的很被动，除了
it may still have enough being going on
它可能仍在继续
sequentially and so it's very important
顺序地，所以这很重要
to actually look at a trace to see if in
实际查看痕迹以查看是否
fact your your requests are doing what
实际上您的请求正在做什么
you think they're doing or if they look
你以为他们在做或者他们在看
like in a trace we talked about like a
就像我们谈论的那样
hysteric hysteric pattern like you can
歇斯底里的歇斯底里模式
just literally see requests going like
只是从字面上看到请求像
this and when you see requests going
这，当您看到请求正在进行时
like this they're not going in parallel
这样他们就不会并行
they're actually going very serial and
他们实际上是非常连续的
so it becomes easier to see these things
所以看这些东西变得更容易
yeah Netflix they're actually hitting to
是的，Netflix实际上是他们
things like and basically if you say it
基本上，如果你说的话
backwards it's DevOps so operational
向后运行DevOps
visibility and developer productivity
知名度和开发人员生产力
and concretely speaking you know in
具体来说，你知道
Netflix so they're using a lot more
Netflix，所以他们使用更多
spring boot they have a lot of older
春季靴他们有很多老
applications also if they're both in the
如果它们都在
same trace it's very a lot easier for
相同的痕迹对于它来说要容易得多
people to have insight about the actual
人们对实际情况有见识
architecture versus just the fraction
建筑而不是分数
that's new and just the fraction as old
这是新的，只是旧的一部分
so it's helpful to get insight over the
因此深入了解
whole thing that's going on the
整个事情正在发生
infrastructure on the tracing backend
跟踪后端的基础架构
basically if people will let down to a
基本上人们是否会失望
couple things in ideal application
理想应用中的几件事
environment your skill sets match your
环境，您的技能与您的技能相匹配
architecture it's the less ideal when
建筑，当它不太理想时
they don't tracing is no different than
他们不追踪与
that so if you create a whole bunch of
因此，如果您创建一大堆
architecture and no one knows how to run
架构，没人知道如何运行
it or develop against it then it's not a
或针对它发展，那不是
happy place you know I've definitely
你知道我绝对快乐的地方
worked at places where you know a team
在您认识团队的地方工作
could kind of left the building
可能会离开建筑物
and then everybody's like this stuff and
然后每个人都喜欢这个东西，
then they just rewrite it right and so
然后他们将其正确重写，如此
the same sorts of stuff if you have
同样的东西，如果你有
anything that the people don't feel
人们感觉不到的任何东西
committed to they call it legacy
致力于他们称之为遗产
and you don't want to be like the legacy
而你不想像传统
thing although you do actually because
事情虽然你实际上是因为
that's the thing making money usually
那就是赚钱的东西
but anyway rambling aside sites have
但不管怎么说，网站都有
different requirements you want to
您想要的不同要求
optimize towards what your skills are so
针对您的技能进行优化
in this case if someone has more
在这种情况下，如果有人有更多
experience in elasticsearch you're
您在Elasticsearch方面的经验
probably going to use the elasticsearch
可能会使用elasticsearch
to Stewart store their traces if they're
斯图尔特存储他们的踪迹，如果他们是
in a says they maybe they're going to
在一个说，他们也许他们将要
use Google Cloud if they're in Google
如果他们在Google中，请使用Google Cloud
Cloud to store their stuff and so that
云存储他们的东西，这样
brings to the point well the does that
很好地指出了这一点
mean a
意思是
Sipkins server is actually in use all
Sipkins服务器实际上正在全部使用
the time no actually we have a lot of
时间不长，实际上我们有很多
sites that don't use Zipkin server
不使用Zipkin服务器的网站
because they are using a sass so for
因为他们用的是无礼的
example if you're using spring cloud
例如，如果您使用的是Spring Cloud
sleuth today you can actually configure
今天您可以实际配置
that directly with a DCP plugin to send
直接用DCP插件发送
directly to stackdriver
直接到堆栈驱动器
trace with no no server infrastructure
在没有服务器基础架构的情况下进行跟踪
at all it can be related to a p.m.
根本可以和一个下午有关
integration a lot of APM products will
集成很多APM产品
accept the Zipkin format whether they
是否接受Zipkin格式
admit it or not usually you can find
承认与否通常可以找到
this out by talking to other customers
通过与其他客户交谈来解决这个问题
and and then you have hybrids where
然后你有混合动力
people for example are storing storing
例如人们正在存储
data for long term analysis and then you
数据进行长期分析，然后您
know so for example in Netflix I think
知道，例如在Netflix，我认为
they and also Expedia they they store
他们和他们存储的Expedia
traces and like s3 for for long term
长期跟踪和喜欢s3
park' like things but the normal trace
公园一样的东西，但正常的痕迹
data is stored for a much shorter period
数据存储时间短得多
of time like three days so that means
大概三天的时间
that it's messy it means that like yeah
这很混乱，这意味着像是
there gonna be some sites that will be
将会有一些网站
using these a beginner of these things
使用这些东西的初学者
are using clones of Zipkin and and it
正在使用Zipkin的克隆，并且
sort of it depends I think one of the
有点取决于我认为
more interesting sites Yelp is this
更多有趣的网站Yelp是这个
thing called like a firehose collectors
像一个消防水枪收藏家的东西
so they want to keep 100% data for for
所以他们想保留100％的数据
like a customer service requests and
如客户服务要求和
things like that and so they have
这样的事情，所以他们有
architecture where
建筑在哪里
they basically store all the data but
他们基本上存储了所有数据，但是
local to Amazon availability zone so
在Amazon可用区本地
they have like Cassandra cluster per
他们每个人都喜欢Cassandra集群
availability zone and they shaved 100%
可用区，他们剃光了100％
data there at the same time that they're
数据同时存在
shooting like 0.01% to a normal server
正常服务器的拍摄速度是0.01％
and if someone is having a question
如果有人有问题
within that buffer of time maybe it's an
在那段时间里也许是
hour then they can always get a trace
一个小时，那么他们总能找到踪影
and whereas usually in distributed
而通常是分布式的
tracing we have this thing called
追踪我们有这个东西叫做
sampling where you're not always taking
采样您并不总是在哪里
a complete trace of the request so
完整的请求跟踪
there's there's some interesting
有一些有趣的东西
interesting patterns that people use I
人们使用我的有趣模式
would call that one a hybrid one where
会把那个叫做混合动力
they're sending to two different
他们要寄给两个不同的人
locations at the same time and you know
位置同时知道
when you're using tracing not
当您使用跟踪不
everybody's using the those same
每个人都在使用相同的
libraries so for example if you're using
库，例如，如果您正在使用
something like this do you I didn't see
这样的事情，你我没看到
like sparkles but you guys aren't
像火花，但你们不是
important anyway that's like envoi is
无论如何，重要的是envoi是
written in C++ right so it's probably
用C ++编写的，所以可能
not going to use like soluz yeah I mean
不会像Soluz那样使用，是的
not C++ so they're gonna be using like
不是C ++，所以他们会像
direct libraries in some cases or the
在某些情况下直接图书馆或
the application frameworks are going to
应用程序框架将
be written different ways so these
被写成不同的方式，所以这些
headers and things we have
标头和我们拥有的东西
specifications for you know how these
规格你知道这些
formats are written so that other
写入格式，以便其他
parties can participate I mean you have
派对可以参加，我是说你有
micro services but everybody has the
微服务，但每个人都有
same library well I mean that's cool
同一个图书馆，我的意思是很酷
that's that's very convenient but but
那很方便，但是
the worlds not always convenient you
世界并不总是方便您
have different different services using
有不同的服务使用
different things and surprisingly enough
不同的事情，令人惊讶的是
in-house tools happen a lot I people may
内部人员经常发生的事
be like scrubbing proxy logs and
就像清理代理日志并
slepping that back into tracing and
将其转回跟踪并
stuff like that so it's it's happens
这样的事情就这样了
more often than you think so
比您想像的更多
one I don't know if it's called a case
我不知道这是否称为案件
study but but here's an interesting one
学习，但这是一个有趣的
that people normally don't talk about
人们通常不会谈论的
when they talk about the projects they
当他们谈论项目时
work on here's a project that stopped
这是一个已停止的项目
using zip code
使用邮政编码
so hotels calm originally started
所以酒店平静最初开始
actually in fact
实际上实际上
Expedia's originally started with with
Expedia最初以
Zipkin as well and the they're actually
Zipkin以及它们实际上是
Expedia companies made an interesting
Expedia公司做了一个有趣的事情
product called haystack which is kind of
一种叫做haystack的产品
like a pretty evolved tool that includes
就像一个非常进化的工具，其中包括
things like alerting which is pretty
诸如警告之类的东西很漂亮
neat
整齐
and so the hotels a calm started with
所以酒店开始平静
with a Zipkin backend and so they're
带有Zipkin后端，因此它们
using apps like sprinkles sleuth and
使用诸如洒侦探和
stuff like that and they want to
这样的东西，他们想
actually send data to to a different
实际将数据发送到另一个
tracing system because the corporate has
跟踪系统，因为公司拥有
this like bigger infrastructure called
这就像更大的基础架构
haystack and so what they've done is
干草堆，所以他们所做的是
they actually still they don't they
他们实际上还是他们不是
don't bother with rewriting their apps
不用担心重写他们的应用程序
to like send arbitrarily into a
喜欢任意发送到
different format they have this this
他们有这个不同的格式
tool called pitchfork which is also a
称为干草叉的工具
spring Buddha I think and that basically
我认为春天的佛陀
just proxies the data out to the other
只是将数据代理给其他人
system because the data formats are
系统，因为数据格式是
usually kind of similar so it's not a
通常有点类似，所以它不是
big deal but when their developers are
没什么大不了的，但是当他们的开发商
doing work because it's a lot easier to
做工作，因为它更容易
deploy Zipkin than it is haystack
部署Zipkin胜过干草堆
haystack you know they have things like
干草堆，你知道他们有这样的事情
terraform and stuff to like spin up the
地形和东西喜欢旋转
things but if you would have that
的东西，但如果你有
compared with like Java - dark you know
与Java相比-黑暗，你知道
maybe some cases you just Java Minister
也许在某些情况下，您只是Java部长
and so their developers when they're
所以他们的开发人员
when they're troubleshooting things they
当他们对问题进行故障排除时
just spin up a local zip code on the
只需在本地旋转邮政编码
workstation and then they can figure out
工作站，然后他们可以找出
what their apps doing and and they don't
他们的应用程序在做什么，而他们没有
have to think about the fact that a
必须考虑以下事实：
production they're using different
生产他们使用不同的
tracing back em so that's kind of
追溯他们，这有点
helpful and so there's a you know a
帮助，所以有一个你知道一个
different site that didn't initially use
最初未使用的其他网站
Zipkin and I'm talking about that I'll
Zipkin和我谈论的是
give you the link later I have in my
稍后给我链接
notes but Netflix I could say like in
笔记，但Netflix我可以说像
2011-2012 a lot of consumer like says
2011-2012年很多消费者喜欢说
companies were making their own tracing
公司进行自己的跟踪
systems Twitter was kind of unique
系统Twitter有点独特
because they
因为他们
open-source tears first but that doesn't
首先是开源眼泪，但这不是
mean that things didn't happen you just
意味着事情没有发生，你只是
didn't see it so so Netflix had their
没看到，所以Netflix有了他们
own tracing system exactly the same time
自己的跟踪系统完全相同
is a lot of companies were doing them
很多公司都在做
and so they had you know you see this
所以他们让你知道你看到了这个
word dapper coming around it's just does
绕过字词修饰符就可以了
a general design and so the a lot of the
一般的设计，所以很多
Java architecture they were using was
他们使用的Java架构是
using a different library and then their
使用不同的库，然后使用
architecture started shifting towards
架构开始向
spring boot and so what they have done
春天的靴子，所以他们做了什么
is a couple things when they retrofitted
他们改装时有几件事
their old libraries to just migrate
他们的旧图书馆只是迁移
things a little bit to use the same
东西有点用一样
header format as as Zipkin uses which is
如Zipkin使用的标头格式是
called B 3 and B 3 stands for Big
被称为B 3和B 3代表Big
Brother bird which which is some nice
兄弟鸟哪位好
true you if you didn't know that and
如果您不知道的话，那么您是真的，并且
that's because the design before Zipkin
那是因为Zipkin之前的设计
was actually a system called Big Brother
实际上是一个叫做“老大哥”的系统
bird and that was when Twitter made all
那只鸟，那是推特的全部作品
services with bird names now what they
现在用鸟名命名的服务
have at Netflix is actually a flink
在Netflix上看其实是一个骗局
pipeline so if link is sort of like
管道，所以如果链接有点像
spark if link people might not
如果链接人可能不会激发
appreciate me describing it like that I
感谢我这样描述我
think it's the streaming architecture
认为这是流媒体架构
and the idea is is that they buffer the
他们的想法是，他们缓冲
data to a certain point where they
数据到某个特定点
realize that it's kind of complete or
意识到这是完整的或
not like maybe I have all of the data
可能我没有所有数据
from all the hosts and then they shoot
从所有主机，然后他们射击
it to analysis and then they also ship
进行分析，然后他们也出货
it to various storage things so in they
它到各种存储的东西，所以在他们
in their pipeline they have data coming
他们的管道中有数据
from the old systems they convert it to
从旧系统将其转换为
zip games format and then the boot apps
压缩游戏格式，然后启动应用程序
are already sending in that and then as
已经在发送，然后作为
it ends up in elasticsearch and other
它最终出现在elasticsearch和其他
things it's all in the same format and
一切都以相同的格式
so it's a lot easier for them to do
所以他们做起来容易得多
aggregations and fancy things with it we
聚合和花式的东西，我们
have a site that has it's never used our
有一个从未使用过的网站
server but are quite prolific
服务器，但产量很高
contributors so in for stellar is a
因此，对于恒星的贡献是
space communications infrastructure firm
太空通讯基础设施公司
in Tokyo so as a startup that does
在东京这样的创业公司
things
东西
rent satellites I think and/or antennas
租用我认为的卫星和/或天线
specifically and so they actually used a
具体来说，所以他们实际上使用了
myriad of different libraries depending
各种不同的库取决于
on what was easiest or whatever they
在最简单的东西上
just decided you'll notice that in a
刚决定，您会注意到
different language like if you're using
不同的语言，例如您使用的是
a certain programming language people
某种编程语言的人
will tend to certain libraries and
将倾向于某些图书馆和
there's a lot of camps in the world
世界上有很多营地
right so the main thing is if they can
对，所以主要的是，如果他们可以
get everything into the same data
将所有内容都放入相同的数据
formats everything's fine and they
格式化一切都很好，他们
actually were the ones that work most on
实际上是最有效的
our google strack driver integration and
我们的google strack驱动程序集成和
so that means that they actually have no
所以这意味着他们实际上没有
no server footprint whatsoever even
甚至没有服务器占用空间
though they're all there
虽然他们都在那里
instrumentation libraries are using
仪器库正在使用
Zipkin format and we have a another site
Zipkin格式，我们还有另一个网站
that's interesting because it has done
这很有趣，因为它已经完成了
not much
不多
notable I think it's also nice to talk
值得注意的是，我也觉得很高兴
about the things that are that are not
关于那些不是
fancy
花式的
so metadata is a an entirely Amazon
所以元数据完全是亚马逊
architecture they use the stock Amazon
他们使用股票的亚马逊架构
zip begin image so they use sqs to send
zip开始图像，以便他们使用sqs发送
the data around and because they don't
周围的数据，因为它们不
have a lot of traffic they're fine to
流量很大，很好
actually collect 100% traces so one
实际上收集了100％的痕迹
thing that's funny is that like if
有趣的是，如果
you're running something like you know a
您正在运行类似您知道的东西
mobile app then you can't really collect
移动应用程序，那么您就无法真正收集
the data for 100% of all of your
100％的数据
communication if you're doing anything
交流，如果您正在做任何事情
like IO T that's not really going to
就像IO T一样，
work either but if you're doing things
也可以，但是如果您在做事
like forms filled out for company or
例如为公司填写的表格或
like high value transactions you can
像高价值的交易，你可以
keep a hundred percent of that so in
保留其中的百分之一百
their case they they choose to collect I
他们的情况下，他们选择收集我
think you even keep it for like a month
以为你甚至保留了一个月
retention because there's no reason for
保留，因为没有理由
them not to so there's no right rule
他们不这样做，所以没有正确的规则
about how much data that you keep it's
关于您保留多少数据
more about how much can you afford to
更多有关您负担得起的费用
keep and what it like ones your storage
保持以及存储的感觉
going to fall over and they did do
要摔倒了，他们确实做到了
something pretty interesting
一些很有趣的东西
the
的
because they know that the data is in
因为他们知道数据在
their case going to elasticsearch
他们的案子要去elasticsearch
although that's not the only storage
虽然这不是唯一的存储空间
option they kind of found a way to like
他们找到了喜欢的方式
do some performance analysis and try to
做一些性能分析，然后尝试
figure out how many people are calling
弄清楚有多少人在打电话
deprecated API s
不推荐使用的API
so once you get these causal causal
所以一旦你得到这些因果因果关系
information that's the that's the cool
信息很酷
stuff where you can find out like okay
可以找到的东西
what patterns of communication are not
没有什么交流方式
not fun so I would say they're stock but
不好玩，所以我会说他们有货，但是
they also add something called slep
他们还添加了一个称为睡眠的东西
which is service level agreement policy
这是服务水平协议政策
I think they just wanted to call it slap
我想他们只是想打巴掌
but basically they made a reporting
但基本上他们做了报告
system that would be slapping people if
会拍人的系统
they messed up someone else's service
他们搞砸了别人的服务
level agreement or they their services
级别协议或其服务
were calling deprecated services and so
正在调用已过时的服务等
they get the slap report sent and it
他们收到了拍打报告，
really helped them drive behavior in the
确实帮助他们推动了行为
company because name and shame is just a
公司，因为名字和耻辱只是一个
very effective tool and you can't see
非常有效的工具，您看不到
it's kind of like fuzzy here but
这里有点像模糊，但是
basically it's not a very fancy UI but
基本上这不是一个非常漂亮的UI，但是
it will show you you this is like logs
它会告诉你这就像日志
that went out of compliance and so they
这超出了合规性，所以他们
have some services that are very green
有一些非常绿色的服务
and some that are very red and so people
还有一些很红，所以人们
get motivated by those things
受到那些事情的激励
so besides architecture like what-what
所以除了像什么的建筑
might be different like I thought I
可能跟我想的不一样
hinted at this and kind of talked about
暗示了这一点，并谈到了
it but data collection policy is is very
它，但是数据收集策略非常
different between sites and I wouldn't
网站之间的差异，我不会
say it's different always meaning that
说总是不同，这意味着
like if people started using the data
就像人们开始使用数据一样
they start figuring out what you know
他们开始弄清楚你所知道的
what what is what is important to talk
什么是重要的谈话
about so for example in type form the
大概是这样，例如
the one that's here right the all their
他们所有在这里的人
apps they always produce a request ID so
应用程序，它们始终会生成请求ID，因此
regardless of whether you're tracing or
不管您是要追踪还是
not they they're using like the kind of
他们使用的不是那种
standard pattern of
的标准模式
an incoming request ID and so they're
传入的请求ID，因此它们是
always doing correlation with that
总是与此相关
that's the most important thing for them
对他们来说最重要的是
is to be able to have their users look
是为了让他们的用户看起来
up things based on request ID and when
根据请求ID和时间
info stellar are working like as opposed
信息恒星像反对一样工作
to Big Macs they're mostly concerned
对于Mac，他们最关心的是
with antennas so they have Auto
与天线，所以他们有自动
completion you know needs that would be
完成，您知道需要
related to two antennas and satellites
与两个天线和卫星有关
because those are actually what what's
因为那些实际上是什么
valuable to the company many companies
对公司很有价值许多公司
have had eras of micro services or
曾经有微服务时代或
digital transformations and each one
数字化转换以及每个
leaves like a stain and your service
像污点一样留下，为您服务
catalog so one of the funny things I
目录，所以我有趣的事情之一
like to see is like when these happen
就像发生这些事情时一样
and you can see like okay everyone
大家都可以看到
decided that the service is called
决定调用该服务
instance today and then like two years
今天，然后像两年
later it's like no it's service and so
后来好像没有服务，所以
now you have both so in their case they
现在你们俩都如此
have some things that are indexed and
有一些被索引的东西
they've trained everyone to look for the
他们训练了所有人寻找
word instance instead of service and so
单词实例代替服务等等
for them they want like the you eyes
对于他们，他们想要像你的眼睛
usually say the word service and they're
通常说服务这个词，他们是
like no please change it to the word
不，请改成单词
instance because it took us like many
实例，因为它使我们像许多人一样
years to come tell people what to use
未来几年告诉人们使用什么
this name so we have to use this name
这个名字，所以我们必须使用这个名字
and phase instead of environment so like
和阶段而不是环境
it's just it's vocab and it sounds silly
只是说唱，听起来很傻
but it's important because
但这很重要，因为
infrastructure teams spend a lot of time
基础架构团队花费大量时间
on this and it can be frustrating if if
在这个问题上，如果
all of that happens and then you have no
所有这些都发生了，那么你就没有了
means to present those words back to the
表示将这些单词返回给
people using this system so and then a
人们使用此系统，然后
funny thing that happens with with
与发生的有趣的事情
public services like Expedia or Netflix
Expedia或Netflix等公共服务
is secret scrubbing so if you have
是秘密擦洗，所以如果你有
things in your traces usually you can
通常情况下，您可以
you know accidentally leak data maybe
你知道偶然泄漏数据
you think you're like logging a prepared
你以为你就像在记录一个准备好的
statement with question marks but there
带有问号的陈述，但在那里
were no question marks and whoops so
没有问号，所以如此
there are you know data collection
你知道数据收集吗
policy depending on whether it's
政策取决于
happening inside of the app like whether
在应用程序内部发生的情况
you're adding a handler to scrub out
您正在添加处理程序以进行清理
some sort of data or whether you're
某种数据或您是否
doing that
那样做
like a rabbitmq listener or whatever
像Rabbitmq监听器或其他
often times there are secrets to scrub I
很多时候有秘密来擦洗我
remember asking folks at Netflix because
记得在Netflix问人们
you know now they're basically a movie
你知道现在他们基本上是电影
production company they're no longer a
生产公司，他们不再是
streaming company and I said do you do
流媒体公司，我说你愿意吗
you scrub or do you have a secret
你擦洗还是有秘密
scrubber and naira responded to me he
洗涤器和奈拉回应我，他
said no we don't we have three you know
说不，我们没有三个，你知道
there's some story about like how some
有一些关于
movies start like got their data about
电影开始像获得有关的数据
their private phone number or whatever I
他们的私人电话号码或任何我
don't remember something like that and
不记得那样的事情了
so like all of a sudden like the answer
就像突然之间的答案一样
is okay three secret scrubbers the other
可以，三个秘密洗涤器，另一个
thing is and I hit this before but like
事情是，我之前打过这个但是
data retention is conditional so Netflix
数据保留是有条件的，因此Netflix
use something called fit so basically
基本上使用所谓的fit
they have a feature flag type of thing
他们有一个特征标记类型的东西
to say if an experiment is going on and
说实验是否正在进行，
believe me you have a lot of experiments
相信我，你有很多实验
going on if you ever using Netflix and
如果您曾经使用Netflix和
so they will during certain experiments
所以他们会在某些实验中
they'll collect 100% of traffic for
他们会收集100％的流量
those type of things into traces and so
那些东西变成痕迹等等
based on headers they decide whether or
根据标头，他们决定是
not to to do that so if you're if you're
不要这样做，如果你是，如果你是
using something like sleuth and you can
使用像侦探一样的东西，你可以
see that there's that ways to change
看到有改变的方式
your sampling policy based on HTTP
您基于HTTP的采样策略
requests and one of the reasons could be
请求，原因之一可能是
that you want to get more traces because
您想要获得更多痕迹，因为
you have something important happening
你正在发生重要的事情
and like there's some sites like
就像有一些网站一样
SoundCloud that that just can't
无法做到的SoundCloud
rationalize storing that much data
合理存储大量数据
because they have so much traffic and so
因为他们有这么多的流量
SoundCloud sample rate is quote unquote
SoundCloud采样率是引用取消引用
very low and maximum 7 days retention
非常低，最多保留7天
sound class is actually a very
声音课实际上是一个非常
interesting site doc to look at because
有趣的网站文档，因为
they they had an interesting way to deal
他们有一种有趣的交易方式
with like this service naming problem
像这样的服务命名问题
and basically they went and they looked
基本上他们去了，他们看着
at the IPS from the kubernetes pods and
在kubernetes窗格中的IPS和
then rewrote the service names
然后改写服务名称
that developers were always using junk
开发人员一直在使用垃圾
and so they would just forget it we
所以他们只会忘记它，我们
can't trust any of this we're gonna cart
不敢相信我们会购物
Blanc rewrite all the service names and
Blanc重写所有服务名称，然后
and so now their service crafts are fun
所以现在他们的服务手艺很有趣
and now if your service names are not
现在，如果您的服务名称不是
correct like what's what's a problem
像什么问题一样正确
what does that happen
那会发生什么
you actually it looks like you're
你实际上看起来像你
calling two different services when
何时调用两种不同的服务
you're actually calling the same one
你实际上是在叫同一个
it's just that this web controller named
只是这个网络控制器命名
it this this web controller named that
这个网络控制器命名为
and so someone who's looking from an
所以有人从
architecture point of view thinks that
建筑学的观点认为
is actually round robin in between
实际上是介于两者之间的循环
different services but so it can get
不同的服务，但它可以得到
messy so one of the most common things
凌乱，这是最常见的事情之一
in all of these sites is you get to a
在所有这些网站中，您都可以
certain point where you're collecting
您正在收集的特定点
the data and you're like that doesn't
数据，而您不会那样
look right and it's it's something that
看起来不错，这就是
you have to you know you end up with
你必须知道你最终会
data policy and and then like all
数据策略，然后像所有
technology adoption it's never really
技术采用从未如此
100% when you get to a complex company
进入一家复杂的公司时100％
and so that's one of the things that's
这是其中的一件事
that's you know interesting sometimes
有时候你知道有趣
one team is responsible for 90% of the
一个团队负责90％的
traffic and so it can sound really neat
交通，所以听起来真的很整洁
that you have like 90 percent of
你有百分之九十的人
requests trace but it's only like one
请求跟踪，但只像一个
team out of like 100 so the numbers
团队人数不超过100，所以数字
alone don't tell the full story
一个人不要讲完整的故事
so anyway I'm gonna leave some minutes
所以无论如何我要离开几分钟
for questions this is the last slide
如有疑问，这是最后一张幻灯片
with content on it and you can come back
上面有内容，您可以回来
to this I'll post the slides but there's
为此，我将发布幻灯片，但是有
there's some archetypes of how people
人们有一些原型
get started and and basically these are
开始，基本上这些是
the ones I've noticed there's the
我注意到的是
Greenfield Greenfield is always easiest
格林菲尔德格林菲尔德总是最简单的
because you just roll out things and you
因为你只是推出东西而你
do what you want right that's why people
做正确的事，这就是为什么人们
who don't work in Greenfield and if
谁在格林菲尔德不工作，如果
you're working in brownfield existing
您在现有的Brownfield工作
environments most people will start with
大多数人会开始使用的环境
a single service just like almost any
几乎任何一项服务
technology and so even what one of the
技术等等
things hotels.com said is even if it's
hotels.com所说的即使是
not actually that distributed you're
其实不是你所散布的
only like one service and is making one
只喜欢一项服务，并且正在提供一项
call to another service the same team
致电同一团队的另一服务
uses you still get insight about like
使用您仍然了解
what's going on and that can be violent
这是怎么回事，这可能是暴力的
with regards to other people being
关于别人
interested in what's what's happening
对正在发生的事情感兴趣
it also helps
这也有帮助
when you look at your service diagram
当您查看服务图时
because you can actually see your
因为你实际上可以看到你的
service diagram grow based on adoption
服务图基于采用情况而增长
and and that can help with with manager
而且可以帮助经理
types with pointy ears and things proxy
尖尖的耳朵和事物代理的类型
is another pattern if you have anything
是另一种模式，如果您有任何东西
in proxy in nature instrumenting that
在自然界中代理
can be helpful so like in type form they
可能会有所帮助，例如以键入形式
they started everything in their proxy
他们开始代理中的一切
because that was easiest way to get some
因为那是获得一些东西的最简单方法
data and then the other thing is just
数据，然后另一件事就是
like slapping it onto a framework
就像将它拍到框架上一样
rollout so if you have like a spring
推出，因此，如果您像春天一样
boot project than just having tracing
引导项目，而不只是进行跟踪
built into that is easy because you
内置于其中很容易，因为您
already have it like you just put sleuth
就像你放侦探一样
in there and so it's an easy answer so
在那里，所以这是一个简单的答案，所以
anyway let's let's wrap up here's the
无论如何，让我们总结一下
link you can start with with questions
可以从问题开始的链接
now for the time between me and beers
现在是我和啤酒之间的时间
we've got we've got some other things so
我们有一些其他的东西，所以
this sites you can actually look in the
您实际上可以在
history and see who's literally editing
历史，看看谁在逐字地编辑
this things you can add a comment to
您可以在此添加评论
them people will answer you so like this
他们会这样回答你的
is this is not like static this is a
这不是静态的吗？
community so do take the to take this
社区，所以要采取这个
information and think of this as as
信息，并认为这是
people like yourselves and ideally some
人们喜欢自己，理想情况下是一些
of you will even post your own site
您甚至会发布您自己的网站
ducks if you're interested in this stuff
鸭子，如果你对此东西感兴趣
we have a gator channel and some of you
我们有一个鳄鱼频道，你们中的一些人
have probably already found it and you
可能已经找到了，你
know if you like what we're doing at add
知道您是否喜欢我们在添加内容时所做的事情
to our star collection so questions so
对我们的明星收藏有疑问
the canonical Zipkin job java so you're
规范的Zipkin工作Java，因此您
asking the canonical is it can Java
问规范是Java吗
library is brave and the first for
图书馆很勇敢，第一个
spring Brut it's actually a slough that
春天的布鲁特实际上是一个泥沼
has a lot of instrumentation integration
有很多仪器集成
and I think Martinez right here can tell
我认为Martinez就可以告诉我们
you that he's spent probably half of
你他花了大概一半的时间
each period of time on a sink so it's a
每个时间在水槽上，所以
pretty important thing and maybe not
非常重要的事情，也许不是
always fun but there's there's
总是很有趣，但是那里有
definitely work there the most important
肯定在那里工作最重要
thing at a sink comes in a couple ways
陷入困境的事情有两种
one is
一个是
when when you have it like a chain of
当你拥有一连串的
events like how the the trace the
事件，如如何跟踪
current trace that's happening gets
当前正在发生的痕迹
moved between each of these phases
在每个阶段之间移动
that's called context propagation and
这称为上下文传播，
there's patterns for that that are in
里面有一些模式
the libraries there and then the other
那里的图书馆，然后另一个
thing is like knowing the difference
事情就像知道差异
between creating the call and invoking
在创建呼叫和调用之间
it so like this assembly time and
像这样的集会时间
runtime of a sync and I wouldn't say
同步运行时，我不会说
that anything is perfect it async is
任何东西都是完美的，它是异步的
where most of the bugs lie but but yeah
大多数错误都在哪里，但是是的
a lot of libraries will have a sync
很多图书馆都会同步
support at this point distributed
此时的支持分布
tracing costs in terms of performance
根据绩效追踪成本
because we are using as you see a spring
因为我们用的就像你看到的弹簧
boot to with spring clouds left with a
引导到春天的云留下一个
brief implementation and we we've made a
简短的实施，我们已经做了一个
test days ago and found that 80 almost
测试几天前，发现80几乎
30% of of performance is lost when when
何时失去30％的性能
using distributed tracing way with a lot
大量使用分布式跟踪方式
of requests and the do you have fun
的请求，你玩得开心吗
insights of the normal performance
正常表现的见解
penalisation of using distributed
使用分布式的惩罚
tracing okay so I think the question is
跟踪好，所以我认为问题是
more when you say cost like I was
当你说我像以前一样花费更多时
actually going to I started looking at
其实我开始看
this which is like we have some people
这就像我们有一些人
who are talking about how many how many
谁在谈论多少
currency units yet in this case they
货币单位，但在这种情况下，它们
were spending on tracing but you're
花费在追踪上，但是你
talking about costs as far as overhead I
就费用而言，我在谈论
think right yeah so the highest overhead
认为是的，所以开销最大
is an async tracing
是异步跟踪
synchronous applications are much
同步应用程序很多
cheaper to trace there's less work
跟踪便宜，工作量少
involved in that and and it's it's a
参与其中，这是一个
it's a moving target so what I always
这是一个移动的目标，所以我一直
say is that when people find a specific
说的是，当人们找到特定的
source of overhead that's higher the
较高的间接费用来源
things that usually affect that or
通常会影响到的事物或
the amount of things that are like
像东西的数量
propagated like there's a way to add
传播就像有一种添加方式
headers and then like called like
标头然后像
baggage and in sleuth terms that that
行李和探秘
tends to slow things down
往往会使事情变慢
synchronizing logs and things like that
同步日志之类的东西
all these features have a calls to them
所有这些功能都可以调用
and so I always say that the there's
所以我总是说
always progress happening here oh
总是进步在这里发生哦
actually I wouldn't say it's always
其实我不会说总是
progress here's why if you move from one
进步就是为什么如果你从一个地方搬走
one type of library to the next
一种类型的库到下一个
sometimes you think that that is going
有时你认为那会发生
to be performance increasing but it may
可以提高性能，但可能
be changes some patterns and it is
被改变一些模式，这是
actually is actually worse for a little
其实稍微差一点
while so I think everybody wants to have
而我想每个人都想拥有
an answer like it's three percent but
答案是百分之三，但是
that never is an answer what you've done
那绝不是你所做的事情的答案
is actually important which is it was a
实际上很重要，那是一个
reactive publication it was that it was
反应性出版物是
not reactive application yeah with
没有反应性的应用耶
buried reactor impact yeah that's the
埋藏的反应堆撞击是的
worst performer that's the worst
表现最差那是最糟糕的
performing under tracing right now and
现在正在追踪下执行
the good news about that is that that
好消息是
means it's probably going to improve but
意味着它可能会有所改善，但是
there are that there are definitely some
肯定有一些
scenarios about that that are inherently
内在的场景
not not performant so when you look at
表现不佳，所以当你看着
tracing you should look at the before
追踪您应该先看一下
and after and it can be tricky to do
之后，这样做可能很棘手
that to be able to be honest one of the
坦白地说，
things that you can do is nice with
你可以做的事情很好
something like sleuth as you can because
像侦探一样，因为
it's spring boots you can do you know
这是春季靴子，你知道吗
something dot enabled and set it to
启用点功能并将其设置为
false and then do your before and after
假，然后做你之前和之后
because that's probably how you came up
因为那可能就是你上来的方式
with whatever the 30 percent is and so
无论30％是多少
when you report an issue if it can be
当您报告问题时
diagnosed to where it's a source of
诊断到它的来源
overhead then that that can help find it
开销，那可以帮助找到它
but I think the the plain truth is is
但我认为一个简单的事实是
that the reactive is is a highest
反应性是最高的
overhead thing to trace at the moment
目前要跟踪的开销的东西
sorry
抱歉
other questions
其他问题
I would tell you some interesting things
我会告诉你一些有趣的事情
about overhead real quick we actually
关于实际开销很快我们实际上
are working on like we have now this
正在像我们现在这样工作
thing how many people have heard of
有多少人听说过的事情
protobuf protocol buffers a lot of
protobuf协议缓冲了很多
people have heard of it
人们听说过
so when you're sent when you're creating
因此，当您在创建时被发送
data for any system and you're sending
您正在发送的任何系统的数据
it out of process like whatever is being
它像任何东西一样无法处理
created even if it's a sink has some
即使它是一个水槽也创建了一些
side effects like extra garbage
额外垃圾等副作用
collection other things like that that
收集其他类似的东西
are going on we have in and the we have
正在进行中，我们进入了
a release happening now in an Zipkin
Zipkin中正在发生的发布
which is not finished being voted on but
尚未完成投票，但
2.14 we have some pretty fun things one
2.14我们有一些很有趣的东西
is we have this thing called storage
我们有这个东西叫做存储吗
throttling which means that everyone is
节流，这意味着每个人都
complaining sometimes about like a set
有时抱怨像一套
elasticsearch falling over and it's like
elasticsearch跌倒了，就像
sending like my cue is too full and
像我的提示一样发送太满，并且
dying and then and then people all their
死亡，然后人们都死了
data gets dropped and so we're using a
数据被删除，因此我们正在使用
really fun library called netflix
真正有趣的库称为netflix
concurrency limits which watches your
并发限制，监视您的
exception patterns and then it will back
异常模式，然后它将返回
off for you it's kind of neat that's a
对你来说这很整洁
tool so we're using it in the server and
工具，所以我们在服务器中使用它
we have a lot of cool efficiency
我们有很多很酷的效率
improvements if you happen to use the
如果您碰巧使用了
protobuf encoding so that's going to be
protobuf编码，因此
probably a little bit of time to get
大概需要一点时间
that into a sleuth dot release because
释放到侦探点中，因为
this hasn't even been released yet but
甚至还没有发布，但是
if you produce JSON the good thing is is
如果您生成JSON，那么好处是
that you can read those requests but you
您可以阅读这些请求，但是您
don't always have to read them yourself
不必总是自己阅读
so if performance is important switching
所以如果性能很重要，切换
to protobuf format even today before
甚至在今天之前也可以使用protobuf格式
this release will will reduce the amount
此版本将减少数量
of garbage created and and the amount of
产生的垃圾数量以及
CPU your process uses it may not have
您的进程使用的CPU可能没有
anything to do with what you're doing
与您正在做的事情有关
but but basically thinking about what's
但基本上是在想什么
going on behind the scenes can help
在幕后进行会有所帮助
reduce this anyway I'll leave you with
减少这种情况我会留给你
with the links I'll put that slide back
与链接，我将把幻灯片放回去
up and thanks for spending time I'll
起，感谢您抽出宝贵的时间，我会
I'll be joining
我会加入
any of you four beers next
你们四个啤酒中的任何一个
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]